I used to live my life a quarter mile at a time.
But things changed.
My father now, I will always be in your heart.
Little Brian, I have a gift for you.
Your daddy gave me this.
No, I'm going to give it to you.
It's very special.
It's for protection from what's coming.
Alright Dom, what's next?
No matter how fast you are.
No one outruns their past.
And mine, just caught up to me for a long time now.
Ex-tabit-la!
So we're up against a master thief, assassin, high-performance driver.
Who is he?
Jacob is Dom's brother.
Your whole life you pushed yourself to be faster than Dom.
Smarter than Dom.
Stronger than Dom.
But could you kill him?
Because I'm ready if you are.
There's nothing more powerful than the love affair, mate.
But you turn that into anger, there's nothing more dangerous.
Maybe this is the end, but we're going to go out together.
You know I'd ride to the death with you.
Let's get to work.
Please tell me that's not a Pontiac Fiera. Strap to a rocket engine?
Impressive, I know.
No, no that's not impressive.
My ass is in play though!
I came here to take you down, little brother.
That's your mistake. This is my world.
Damn, they got a magnet plane?
Hold on.
Tell me you're not thinking what I think you're thinking.
There's no bridge!
Oh, hell no.
Hey guys.
Surprise.
Nice clubhouse.