We will leave without listening to the Azan and watch the time without you.
Look at the car's ticket.
Because we are going to Medina now.
And the challenge for us today is that we have to leave on the highway.
And remember to take the khujur from the car.
What a great thing.
That day, the khujur that Majid brother brought,
Majid brother will meet us again today.
So, Aslam o alaikum wa rahmatullah wa baraka'atuh.
I am Abdul Malik Fareed with Mamu Sameer and Moiz.
I am Madina Chaloo, I am Madina Chaloo.
This is the house of the Prophet.
I am there.
O my Mola, listen to me.
Since when have you been waiting for this heart?
Today, we have decided that we will leave without listening to the Azan and watch the time without you.
We will watch the time without listening to the Azan.
That is because the real way of sunset is the time of Maghrib prayer.
Then, inshaAllah, we will leave everyday and we will show you that the sun must have been set.
And today's our departure will be at the speed of 140.
And here, the legal speed is of 140.
Which goes from Makkah to Medina.
The sun has almost set.
I can see the sun's light for a moment.
Let's cross the mountain and confirm it.
Then, we will leave everyday.
In Saudi Arabia, the sun is a bit visible.
Especially in the mountainous area, it is hidden behind the mountain.
The sun has set.
Only the red light is visible.
So, it is time for our departure.
In the name of Allah.
Thank you.
Let's confirm it.
The sun has set.
Today's departure is at the speed of 140.
InshaAllah.
Bismillah.
Now, we have stopped here at the sasco.
This is in front of you.
We will have Albaik.
Uncle is going to get the petrol.
Till then, the petrol will be added.
You also do something.
They are adding petrol.
I will eat it.
Yes, this is the guest's food.
I thought that Albaik will be up and down.
It will be up and down.
Now, the Albaik people have said that they will take 20 minutes to make fresh.
Till then, let's take some water, some lentils.
Here you go, guest.
You can take whatever you want.
How will you keep it?
Keep whatever you want.
No, you can't.
Let's take Laban.
Laban is mango.
Mango?
Yes.
Will it be a wedding?
Will it be sweet?
Of course, it will be sweet.
Let it be.
I am looking for some juice.
This is good water.
3 water has come.
What else to take?
This is a big Laban.
This is a small Laban.
This is a sweet one.
Laban is over.
The time for the Eftar is over.
We will drink this.
Mango and I like this.
Keep it here.
Peace be upon you.
What is your name?
My name is Zeeshan.
Zeeshan?
Yes.
You watch the vlog?
Our drinks have come.
We are hungry because of this.
We have taken 3 drinks.
One juice, one water and one lassi.
Mango Laban.
This is the park behind this al-baik.
We sit here often.
And we will sit here today.
Since we have taken this from Abdul Rahman.
We have not taken it back.
You will get the answer.
We have made 4 videos like this.
We give our friends your chance.
Let's go.
Our Moiz brother said that he wants to eat a burger.
Yes.
Give him a burger.
Let's leave him alone.
Let's go.
Go.
Who are you?
This is your burger.
This is not good.
You said that you want to eat a burger.
This is a double patty burger.
The burger that was in the picture was 2 kg.
They all look like big burgers.
They are big.
I am dead.
What should we do?
You are responsible for this.
I will give you one negative.
I will take one by one.
One by one.
I will not give you one by one.
You will get one by one.
You are not making the decision of the cats.
Moiz, eat whatever you want.
But don't stop us from eating burgers.
I mean eat burgers first.
Eat.
Don't stop us from eating burgers.
This is cheese.
The weather is cool here.
It is very cold.
I am hungry today.
The nuggets are also delicious.
We have taken two burgers and two nuggets.
We will take 10 pieces.
We will be full.
I have brought this cheese.
Especially this one.
Don't serve it.
No.
This is called normal.
And this is according to the normal.
It is so cold.
We will meet you in Madina.
How is the food?
First time seeing the food.
It is different.
It is a little less.
He doesn't let us hear.
You get connected.
Alhamdulillah, we came here after saying hello.
We are about to drink Zamzam.
But there is another story in Zamzam.
This is our Moiz.
We came here for the first time.
It was the first time when we had Umrah.
Yes.
We didn't get the food.
We came to Madina and immediately after the Al-Azizaharad.
Yes.
What a thing.
Alhamdulillah.
When we come here, we say hello.
And we come to the mosque.
We pray.
We get so much peace.
Which is not possible in words.
I thought for a long time.
I thought that I could give an example of this.
But I couldn't give an example.
I thought for a long time.
I came here to give an example of peace.
When you keep your mother's burden.
How do you feel peace?
But it is more than that.
I didn't understand that.
I didn't understand that this is also an example.
What is the reason for giving an example?
Alhamdulillah.
Now, when you see in the video.
You must feel so peace.
But in fact, it is much more than that.
The more you see in the video.
It is much more than that.
I just pray to Allah.
All the people who are watching this.
May Allah give them a lot of peace.
This is a prayer from my heart.
Look, here is a special place for special people.
It is kept near the door.
You enter from here.
The special people are given a place here.
That is, no one else is allowed to sit here.
The wheel chairs are standing here.
That is a special person.
Alhamdulillah, the visit has also taken place.
In Masjid-e-Nabwi.
Which Allah has given a gift.
Alhamdulillah, it has gone.
And today's video ends here.
Alhamdulillah, Madinatul-Munawra is here.
Some people will go to Madinatul-Munawra.
Some people will go to the malls.
What a place of peace.
Alhamdulillah, Allah has given a gift.
Come here.
And for you all, many prayers are for me.
From my side.
May Allah give you the best of the world.
I will show you my love in videos.
As always.
And InshaAllah, I will meet you in the next video.
Allah Hafiz.