The next day
Outfit X is a private terror group
which doesn't work for any purpose.
They work on contracts.
Ma'am, we have a red flag.
They are planning on a massive attack.
And their target is India.
An attack that India never thought of.
It's not a negotiation.
It's ultimate.
And your time starts...
now.
So now?
Now the time for the revolution is over.
The party will be kept at the revolution house.
The revolution will come for you to die.
The revolution will come for you.
And the revolution will come for you.
I am a soldier, Patan. Like you.
We can do this mission together.
So are you in? Or are you out?
A single number of severed lives
will be the result of a moment in time
before the revolution comes down.
Patan, the hundred...
hundred?
Let's go.
Say my last salute to your mother India.
A soldier doesn't ask what the country did for him.
He asks what the country can do for him.
Jai Hind.