I know that this road has been very hard.
And yet here you are, building this magnificent family.
What's going on in that head of yours?
Something little beast that I...
I said, dad, they're not afraid of anything.
But I am.
I'm afraid of losing someone I love.
Dominic Toretto.
You're about to learn all about fear.
Boom!
You built such a beautiful life filled with love and family.
I never got that chance.
You stole that from me.
My future.
My family.
And now, I'm gonna break yours.
Peace by peace.
He's coming through you with everything.
What's the plan, Dom?
I'm not sure anymore.
One of us might not come back from this.
But we have to fight.
Never accept death.
When suffering is owed.
He's coming!
All the dangerous.
Ain't too many good things with us.
Labour loves no glorious.
This is setup.
He's trying to tear us apart.
Constituation is fight one.
What's one of you?
I got one.
When it used to be about winning,
we raised for respect.
Today, I raised to stop the bloodbath.
That's the problem with having such a big family.
How do you choose the ones you save?
Let's race!
You still know how to drive?
What do you think?
It's showtime!
Here we go!
Game recognizes game.
I'm coming for you, son.
Here they come.
You will never be able to break my family.
No!
Good morning, sunshine.
You gotta be kidding me.